Soviet Union and Russia Orthodox Subject Files, Inclusive: 1922 — 2018, undated, Bulk: 1970-1992
Baylor University, The Keston Center for Religion, Politics, and Society
- General, 1922-2018, undated; 1
  - Imprisonment of Members of the Russian Orthodox Church. Krakhmal'nikova, Zoia, Svetov, Feliks, 1979, 1982-1986, 2008, undated (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Imprisonment of Members of the Russian Orthodox Church. Kukobaka, Mikhail, 1979-1988 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Imprisonment of Members of the Russian Orthodox Church. Lazareva, Natal'ia, 1981-1986 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Imprisonment of Members of the Russian Orthodox Church. Lysak, Fr. Pavel, 1984-1985 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Imprisonment of Members of the Russian Orthodox Church. Markus, Sergei, 1984-1986 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Imprisonment of Members of the Russian Orthodox Church. Meilakh, Mikhail, 1983-1984 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Imprisonment of Members of the Russian Orthodox Church. Ogorodnikov, Aleksandr, 1979-1986 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Imprisonment of Members of the Russian Orthodox Church. Ogurtsov, Igor, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Imprisonment of Members of the Russian Orthodox Church. Oros, Oleksandr, 1974, 1979-1985, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Imprisonment of Members of the Russian Orthodox Church. Osipov, Vladimir, 1980, 1984, undated (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Imprisonment of Members of the Russian Orthodox Church. Pivovarov, Aleksandr, 1983, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Imprisonment of Members of the Russian Orthodox Church. Poresh, Vladimir, 1979-1986 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Imprisonment of Members of the Russian Orthodox Church. Protsenko, Pavel, 1986-1987 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Imprisonment of Members of the Russian Orthodox Church. Ratushinskaia, Irina, 1983-1985 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Imprisonment of Members of the Russian Orthodox Church. Razveev, Boris, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Imprisonment of Members of the Russian Orthodox Church. Regel'son, Lev, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Imprisonment of Members of the Russian Orthodox Church. Romaniuk, Vasyl', 1987 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Imprisonment of Members of the Russian Orthodox Church. Rusak, Fr. Vladimir, 1979-1987, undated (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Imprisonment of Members of the Russian Orthodox Church. Safronov, Fr. Iosif, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Imprisonment of Members of the Russian Orthodox Church. Senderov, Valerii, 1982-1987 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Imprisonment of Members of the Russian Orthodox Church. Sannikova, Elena, 1984, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Imprisonment of Members of the Russian Orthodox Church. Shchipkova, Tat'iana, 1979-1983 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Imprisonment of Members of the Russian Orthodox Church. Velikanova, Tat'iana, 1979-1987 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - State Interference in the Affairs of the Russian Orthodox Church, 1967-1987 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Refusal to Register. Closure of Churches (1 of 2), 1930-1988 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Refusal to Register. Closure of Churches (2 of 2), 1989-1992, undated (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. State Interference in Parish Life, 1974-1988 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. State Interference in Affairs of Clergy, 1976-1989, undated (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Infiltration into Affairs of the Russian Orthodox Church (1 of 3), 1958-1991 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Infiltration into Affairs of the Russian Orthodox Church (2 of 3), 1992 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Infiltration into Affairs of the Russian Orthodox Church (3 of 3), 1993-2002 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. State Interference in the Affairs Monasteries, 1980-1987, undated (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. State Interference in Religious Education, 1976-1987 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. State Interference in Religious Literature, 1976-1984 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. State Expropriation, Desecration and Demolition of Church Buildings, 1974-1991, undated (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Discrimination against Orthodox Believers in Employment, 1976-1987 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Discrimination against Orthodox Believers in Education, 1930, 1977-1983 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Misuse of Psychiatry toward Orthodox Believers (1 of 2), 1973-1979 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Misuse of Psychiatry toward Orthodox Believers (2 of 2), 1980-1989, undated (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Misuse of Psychiatry toward Orthodox Believers. Valeriia Makeeva, 1979-1981, undated (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Public Attacks on Orthodox Believers in Media, 1960-1989, undated (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Searchers of Orthodox Believers Houses, 1976-1987, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Loss of Parental Rights by Orthodox Believers, 1977-1978, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Russian Orthodox Church Life (1 of 2), 1973-1987 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Russian Orthodox Church Life (2 of 2), 1988-1998, undated (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Russian Orthodox Church Life. Festivals. Anniversaries (1 of 7), 1962-1979 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Russian Orthodox Church Life. Festivals. Anniversaries (2 of 7), 1980-1985 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Russian Orthodox Church Life. Festivals. Anniversaries (3 of 7), 1986 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Russian Orthodox Church Life. Festivals. Anniversaries (4 of 7), 1987 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Russian Orthodox Church Life. Festivals. Anniversaries (5 of 7), 1988 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Russian Orthodox Church Life. Festivals. Anniversaries (6 of 7), 1990-1991 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Russian Orthodox Church Life. Festivals. Anniversaries (7 of 7), 1992-1998, 2007, undated (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Millennium and SOBOR. General, 1983-1988, undated (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Millennium and SOBOR. Letters from Christians, 1987-1988, undated (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Millennium and SOBOR. The Statute of the Government of the Russian Orthodox Church (1 of 2), 1988 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Millennium and SOBOR. The Statute of the Government of the Russian Orthodox Church (2 of 2), 1988 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Millennium and SOBOR. Russian Orthodox Church and Ecumenical Movements (manuscript), 1987 July-1988 May (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Millennium and SOBOR. Anniversary Publications of the Russian Orthodox Church, 1988 May (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Millennium and SOBOR. Russian Orthodox Church's Relations with Churches of Other Denominations (manuscript), undated (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Millennium and SOBOR. Manuscripts, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Millennium and SOBOR. John Paul II's Apostolic Letter, 1988 January 25 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Millennium and SOBOR. General (1 of 2), 1988 January-May (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Millennium and SOBOR. General (2 of 2), 1988 June-December (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Millennium and SOBOR. Soviet Press Articles, 1988-1989 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Millennium and SOBOR. Documents of Pre-Council Meeting of Bishops, 1988 March 28-31 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Millennium and SOBOR. Program of Events, 1988 June 4-17 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Millennium and SOBOR. Ritual Observance of Celebration of the Baptism of Rus', 1988 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Millennium and SOBOR. Documents of SOBOR, 1988 June 6-9 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Millennium and SOBOR. Canonization, 1988 June 6-9 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Millennium and SOBOR. Report on Canonization, 1988 June 6-9 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Millennium and SOBOR. Report on the Statute of the Russian Orthodox Church, 1988 June 6-9 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Millennium and SOBOR. Report on Economic Activity of the Russian Orthodox Church, 1988 June 6-9 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Millennium and SOBOR. Report on the Russian Orthodox Church's External Relations, 1988 June 6-9 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Millennium and SOBOR. Presentation on the Millennium of the Baptism of Russia, 1988 June 6-9 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Millennium and SOBOR. Presentation on the Millennium of the Baptism of Russia (German), 1988 June 6-9 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Millennium and SOBOR. Report on Peacemaking Activities of the Russian Orthodox Church, 1988 June 6-9 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Millennium and SOBOR. Report on Publishing Activity of the Russian Orthodox Church, 1988 June 6-9 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Millennium and SOBOR. Report on Spiritual Formation and Theological Education in the Russian Orthodox Church, 1988 June 6-9 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Millennium and SOBOR. Report of Patriarchal Exarch to Western Europe, Chancellor of the Moscow Patriarchate, 1988 June 6-9 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Russian Orthodox Church Life. Canonization, 1977-2000, undated (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Russian Orthodox Church Life. Services. Liturgy (1 of 2), 1951-1973 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Russian Orthodox Church Life. Services. Liturgy (2 of 2), 1974-1999, undated (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Russian Orthodox Church Life. Services. Liturgy. Brochures, 1947-1983, undated (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Russian Orthodox Church Life. Attraction of Liturgy, 1963-1989 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Russian Orthodox Church Life. Bell Ringing, 1961-1998 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Russian Orthodox Church Life. Modernization, 1966-1988, 1994-1995 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Russian Orthodox Church Life. Pilgrimages. Holy places, 1966-2001, undated (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Russian Orthodox Church Life. Saints and Holy Men, 1974-2005, undated (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Preaching. Evangelism. Conversions, 1959-2001, undated (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Parish Life, 1975-1995, undated (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Defection from Orthodox Faith, 1962-1987 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Russian Orthodox Church Publications. General (1 of 2), 1955-1984 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Russian Orthodox Church Publications. General (2 of 2), 1985-1996, undated (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Russian Orthodox Church Publications. The Journal of the Moscow Patriarchate (1 of 3), 1959-1973 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Russian Orthodox Church Publications. The Journal of the Moscow Patriarchate (2 of 3), 1974-1975 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Russian Orthodox Church Publications. The Journal of the Moscow Patriarchate (3 0f 3), 1976-1986 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Russian Orthodox Church Publications. Bogoslovskie Trudy, 1982-1983 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Revival, 1966-2001, undated (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Excommunication, 1978-1979 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Monasticism. General (1 of 4), 1961-1975 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Monasticism. General (2 of 4), 1976-1985 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Monasticism. General (3 of 4), 1986-1993 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Monasticism. General (4 of 4), 1994, undated (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Monasticism. Danilov Monastery, 1983-1989 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Monasticism. Kiev-Pechersk-Lavra, 1959-1995, undated (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Monasticism. Optina Pustyn', 1979-1993, undated (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Monasticism. Pochayev Lavra (1of 3), 1962-1971 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Monasticism. Pochayev Lavra (2 of 3), 1971-1991 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Monasticism. Pochayev Lavra (3 of 3), undated (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Monasticism. Pskovo-Pechersk Monastery, 1954-1992, undated (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Monasticism. Puhtitsa Monastery, 1972-1991, undated (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Monasticism. Solovki (1 of 2), 1976-2003, undated (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Monasticism. Solovki (2 of 2), undated (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Monasticism. Trinity-St. Sergius Lavra in Zagorsk, 1958-1993, undated (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Russian Orthodox Church Life. Union of Orthodox Brotherhoods, 1990-1994 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Orthodox Church Life. Herald of the Union of Orthodox Brotherhoods, 1991-1992 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Russian Orthodox Church Life. Philanthropy, 1980-1997 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Clergy. Priesthood, 1962-1998, undated (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Hierarchy. General (1 of 2), 1964-1972 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Hierarchy. General (2 of 2), 1973-1999 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Hierarchy. Lists of Bishops (1 of 2), 1944-1980 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Hierarchy. Lists of Bishops (2 of 2), 1969-1988 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Ordinations. Elections. Retirements, 1961-1999, undated (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Election of Patriarch Aleksii II, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Individual Russian Orthodox Clergy. General, 1967-2000 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Individual Russian Orthodox Clergy. A-B, 1962-1987 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Individual Russian Orthodox Clergy. I-N, 1961-1989 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Individual Russian Orthodox Clergy. P-V, 1966-1991 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Individual Russian Orthodox Clergy. Adelgeim (Adelheim), Fr. Pavel (1 of 2), 1970-2013 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Individual Russian Orthodox Clergy. Adelgeim (Adelheim), Fr. Pavel (2 of 2), 1970-2013 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Individual Russian Orthodox Clergy. Aleksandr (Pivovarov), Protopriest, 1983-1989, 2006 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Individual Russian Orthodox Clergy. Aleksii I (Simanskii), Patriarch, 1963-1975 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Individual Russian Orthodox Clergy. Aleksii II (Ridiger), Patriarch (1 of 4), 1977-1990 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Individual Russian Orthodox Clergy. Aleksii II (Ridiger), Patriarch (2 of 4), 1991-1993 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Individual Russian Orthodox Clergy. Aleksii II (Ridiger), Patriarch (3 of 4), 1994-1995 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Individual Russian Orthodox Clergy. Aleksii II (Ridiger), Patriarch (4 of 4), 1996, 1999, 2001 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Individual Russian Orthodox Clergy. Anthony (Bloom), Metropolitan of Sourozh, 1974-2018, undated (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Individual Russian Orthodox Clergy. Borisov, Fr. Aleksandr, 1993-1994 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Individual Russian Orthodox Clergy. Chrysostom, Archbishop of Kursk and Belgorod, 1979, 1981 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Individual Russian Orthodox Clergy. Dudko, Fr. Dmitry (1 of 8), 1972-1974 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Individual Russian Orthodox Clergy. Dudko, Fr. Dmitry (2 of 8), 1975 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Individual Russian Orthodox Clergy. Dudko, Fr. Dmitry (3 of 8), 1976 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Individual Russian Orthodox Clergy. Dudko, Fr. Dmitry (4 of 8), 1977-1978 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Individual Russian Orthodox Clergy. Dudko, Fr. Dmitry (5 of 8), 1979 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Individual Russian Orthodox Clergy. Dudko, Fr. Dmitry (6 of 8), 1980 January-June (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Individual Russian Orthodox Clergy. Dudko, Fr. Dmitry (7 of 8), 1980 July-December (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Individual Russian Orthodox Clergy. Dudko, Fr. Dmitry (8 of 8), 1981-2013, undated (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Individual Russian Orthodox Clergy. Edelshtein, Fr. Georgii (Fr. Georgy Edelstein), 1988-1999 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Individual Russian Orthodox Clergy. Ermogen (Hermogen)(Golubev), Archbishop, 1953-1987 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Individual Russian Orthodox Clergy. Eshliman, Fr. Nikolai and Yakunin, Fr. Gleb (1 of 2), 1966 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Individual Russian Orthodox Clergy. Eshliman, Fr. Nikolai and Yakunin, Fr. Gleb (2 of 2), 1970-1976 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Individual Russian Orthodox Clergy. Eshliman, Fr. Nikolai, 1985, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Individual Russian Orthodox Clergy. Filaret (Denisenko), Metropolitan of Kyiv and Halych, 1975-1992 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Individual Russian Orthodox Clergy. Filaret (Vakhromeev), Metropolitan of Minsk and Belorussia, 1979-1989 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Individual Russian Orthodox Clergy. Ioann (Snychev), Metropolitan of Saint Petersburg and Ladoga (1 of 2), 1992-1993 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Individual Russian Orthodox Clergy. Ioann (Snychev), Metropolitan of Saint Petersburg and Ladoga (2 of 2), 1993-1995 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Individual Russian Orthodox Clergy. Iosif, Archbishop of Ivano-Frankovsk and Kolomyia, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Individual Russian Orthodox Clergy. Iov (Kresovich), Archbishop of Ivanovo and Kineshma, 1960-1978 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Individual Russian Orthodox Clergy. Iuvenalii (Poiarkov), Metropolitan of Krutitsy i Kolomna, 1970-1996 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Individual Russian Orthodox Clergy. Kirill (Gundiaev), Patriarch, 1989-1999, 2002, undated (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Individual Russian Orthodox Clergy. Kochetkov, Fr. Georgii, 1992-1998, undated (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Individual Russian Orthodox Clergy. Lazar (Lasar) (Solnyshko), Hegumen, 1990-1991 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Individual Russian Orthodox Clergy. Luka (Voino-Yasenetsky), Archbishop, 1957, 1978-1979, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Individual Russian Orthodox Clergy. Manuil (Lemeshevsky), Metropolitan, 1968, 1973, 1976 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Individual Russian Orthodox Clergy. Nikodim (Rotov), Metropolitan of Leningrad and Novgorod, 1960-1980, 1983, 1988 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Individual Russian Orthodox Clergy. Pavel (Golyshev), Archbishop of Vologda and Novosibirsk, 1969-1977 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Individual Russian Orthodox Clergy. Philaret (Voznesensky), Metropolitan (ROCOR), 1976, undated (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Individual Russian Orthodox Clergy. Pimen (Izvekov), Patriarch, (1 of 2), 1965-1981 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Individual Russian Orthodox Clergy. Pimen (Izvekov), Patriarch (2 of 2), 1982-1995, undated (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Individual Russian Orthodox Clergy. Pitirim (Nechaev), Metropolitan of Volokolams and Iur'ev, 1974-2003 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Individual Russian Orthodox Clergy. Romaniuk, Fr. Vasil' (Vasilii), 1972-1988, 1993, 1995, undated (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Individual Russian Orthodox Clergy. Romaniuk, Fr. Vasil' (Vasilii). Sermons, 1977, 1980-1983 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Individual Russian Orthodox Clergy. Sergii (Stargorodskii), Patriarch, 1979, 1981, 1999, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Individual Russian Orthodox Clergy. Shpiller, Fr. Vsevolod, Archpriest, 1963-1984 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Individual Russian Orthodox Clergy. Tikhon (Bellavin), Patriarch, 1922-1925, 1974, 1977, 1989 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Individual Russian Orthodox Clergy. Yakunin, Fr. Gleb (1 of 12), 1974-1976 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Individual Russian Orthodox Clergy. Yakunin, Fr. Gleb (2 of 12), 1977 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Individual Russian Orthodox Clergy. Yakunin, Fr. Gleb (3 of 12), 1978-1979 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Individual Russian Orthodox Clergy. Yakunin, Fr. Gleb (4 of 12), 1980 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Individual Russian Orthodox Clergy. Yakunin, Fr. Gleb (5 of 12), 1981 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Individual Russian Orthodox Clergy. Yakunin, Fr. Gleb (6 of 12), 1982-1985 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Individual Russian Orthodox Clergy. Yakunin, Fr. Gleb (7 of 12), 1987-1989 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Individual Russian Orthodox Clergy. Yakunin, Fr. Gleb (8 of 12), 1990-1991 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Individual Russian Orthodox Clergy. Yakunin, Fr. Gleb (9 of 12), 1992 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Individual Russian Orthodox Clergy. Yakunin, Fr. Gleb (10 of 12), 1993 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Individual Russian Orthodox Clergy. Yakunin, Fr. Gleb (11 of 12), 1994 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Individual Russian Orthodox Clergy. Yakunin, Fr. Gleb (12 of 12), 1995-1999, 2015, undated (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Individual Russian Orthodox Clergy. Zalivako, Fr. Boris, 1971, 1973-1975, 1977, 1978 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Individual Russian Orthodox Clergy. Zharkov, Fr. Aleksandr, 1997 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Individual Russian Orthodox Clergy. Zheludkov, Fr. Sergei, 1961-1977, 1984, 1987, undated (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Working and Living Conditions of Russian Orthodox Clergy, 1977, 1979-1982, 1984, 1988-1989, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Russian Orthodox Clergy and Priesthood. Statistics, 1974, 1978-1980, 1987-1989 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. International Contacts. General, 1976-1995 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. International Contacts. Countries A-Z, 1962-1999, undated (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Western Reaction. Aid. Solidarity. Protests (1 of 2), 1963-1980 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Western Reaction. Aid. Solidarity. Protests (2 of 2), 1980-1988, 1991, 2001, undated (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Contacts with International Organizations, 1976-1989 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Soviet Delegations Visits Abroad, 1972-1998 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Visits from Foreign Delegations (1 of 2), 1967-1977 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Visits from Foreign Delegations (2 of 2), 1977-1990 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Illegal and Underground Activities, 1962-1988 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Meetings. Prayer Groups. Rites. Ceremonies, 1962-2007 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Individual Russian Orthodox Dissidents, 1976-1980 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Public Demonstrations. Protests, 1975-2001 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Defense of Believers' Rights, 1976, 1980-1988 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Criticism of Church Policy by Believers. General, 1966-1989 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Criticism of Church Policy by Believers. Vladyka Isidor, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Criticism of Church Policy by Believers. Church and Perestroika, 1990-1996 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Emigration on Religious Grounds, 1976-1988 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Contacts with Foreigners, Emigres, etc., 1982, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Underground Publications. General, 1976-1989 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Underground Publications. Beseda, 1976, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Underground Publications. In Light of Transfiguration, 1978-1980 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Underground Publications. Maria, 1981-1982 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Underground Publications. Mnogaia Leta, 1980-1984 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Underground Publications. Nadezhda, 1978-1988, undated (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Underground Publications. Obshchina, 1978-1979 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Samizdat, 1959-1979 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Unofficial Religious Education, 1979 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Unofficial Ecumenical Contacts, 1979 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Underground Production of Religious Literature, 1966-1972, 1982-1989 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Dissenting Religious Youth, 1979, 1980 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Charitable Activity, 1983, 1988 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Theology. Philosophy. Education. Ethics., 1966-1978 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Theology, 1959-1992 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Individual Theologians, 1974-2007 (Box 29, Folder 1)